So, look, I-I wasn't going
to say anything,
(Amy:)but since you seem to be okay
with the article being canceled,
(Amy:)I have a little confession.
(Amy:)I'm the reason it was pulled.
(Bernadette:)What? How?
(Amy:)I sent the editors
of the magazine
(Amy:)a pretty scathing e-mail.
(Bernadette:)Amy, what did you say?
(Amy:)I simply pointed out
(Amy:)that they would never consider
doing an article
(Amy:)ranking male scientists
on their sexuality,
(Amy:)let alone showing them
in various stages of undress.
(Bernadette:)Because no one wants to see
Neil deGrasse Tyson
(Bernadette:)in a wet T-shirt,
bent over the hood of a Porsche.
(Amy:)Well, it doesn't
make a difference,
(Amy:)because they agreed it was
in bad taste,
(Amy:)and now you agree, so...
(Amy:)Amy saves the day.
(Bernadette:)No, what happened was
you got jealous,
(Bernadette:)so you took away a chance
for me to get some publicity.
(Amy:)But it was bad publicity.
(Bernadette:)That's for me to decide,
not you.
(Amy:)I disagree.
(Amy:)As a female scientist, I think
what you do affects all of us.
(Bernadette:)And I think
you don't like people
(Bernadette:)expressing their sexuality